MARCEL MOTTA



PROFILE

Name

Marcel Motta do Nascimento

Praça Teófilo Braga, 10/8D Lisbon

Phone

+351 916262176

marcel.motta@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Brazilian, 30 years-old, living by learning something new everyday. I'm looking forward to working with innovative and creative people who are willing to make a difference. I have a deep interest in science and technology and I believe that they are the right tools for making people's lives better. For this reason, I decided to study and work for the IT industry, to fully understand how businesses and individuals can go beyond by working side-by-side and, ultimately, build a brighter future.

SOCIAL



twitter.com/marcelmotta



in linkedin.com/in/marcelmotta



S marcel.motta

EXPERIENCE

IT Business Analyst

IT project management analyst, ensuring security requirements and monitoring access control for supported applications, preparation of compliance and audit reports, monitoring Latin America pricing activities on z/OS environment by using DB2 SQL and MVS applications, managing innovation initiatives and process enhancements through IBM

Connections social platform. Sales Support Analyst

Jan 2012 - Oct 2014

Jan 2011 - Jan 2012

Oct 2014 - Oct 2015

Supporting sales operations for United States and Canada accounts, monitoring customers inventory, providing financial reports and creating lease proposals by using DB2 SQL, MVS applications, Brio/Hyperion and SAP ERP.

Billing Analyst

Processing and invoicing leasing transactions for United States and Canada customers by using MVS applications and SAP ERP, preparation of transaction reports with DB2 SQL and Brio/Hyperion for audit purposes.

EDUCATION

MSc in Knowledge Management and Business Intelligence

Universidade Nova de Lisboa - Portugal

BSc in International Relations

Universidade Estácio de Sá - Brazil

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified Scrum Master

TECH SKILLS













LANGUAGES

Google Analytics IQ



Scrum Alliance

2015

Google 2015





